MARCUS MATTHEWS

(703)-606-4882

MLMatthews75@gmail.com

3162 Crab Trap Drive New Smyrna, FL 32168

PROFILE

Maximize my skills, experience and education as an employee of a successful company and have my accomplishments recognized with job growth. Miami University Student-Athlete graduate that demonstrates great communication with others and is excellent in time management and leadership. Highly motivated and organized with the ability to work successfully in team settings.

EXPERIENCE

General Manager, Massey Services, Inc., Ormond Beach, FL 2020-Present

- Oversees service center operations that include sales, customer service, profit & loss, budget implementation and problem solving
- Heading the recruitment process which involves communicating, interviewing and hiring prospective team members for all positions within the service center
- Creating and implementing service center budgets as well as controlling costs in all aspects of daily operations
- Execution of policy and procedure as a General Manager along with upholding accountability of other team members for their respected policies and procedures
- · Meeting deadlines of daily, weekly and monthly tasks

Assistant Manager, Enterprise Rent-A-Car, Front Royal, VA 2017-2020

- Utilize customer service, sales, marketing and employee management on a daily basis
- Implementing problem solving strategies and being solution oriented
- Maintain corporate accounts to ensure a strong professional relationship
- Managing and maintaining a fleet of 200+ vehicles
- Teaching, coaching and implementing core values to employees that can lead them to future success with company

Legal Assistant, Shapiro & Brown LLP, Manassas, VA 2015-2017

- Working in Document Execution, providing clients with documents needed to proceed with various legal processes
- Correcting, enhancing and preparing documents using Microsoft office to meet the desired needs of our clients
- Speaking with clients directly via phone calls and emails, giving feedback on how documents can be improved and revised

 Meeting deadlines and expectations of clients on a daily basis in order to uphold a great relationship with the firm

Sports Marketing Intern, Miami University, Oxford, OH 2015

- Worked with a variety of Winter and Spring sports maintaining and conducting different behind-the-scene duties
- Implementing numerous marketing strategies to improve crowd involvement and overall satisfaction
- Observing positive and/or negative crowd response to in-game entertainment that also involved communicating with fans and colleagues about marketing expectations
- Providing an exciting experience during their experience at a Miami University athletic event

EDUCATION

Miami University, Oxford, Ohio — Bachelors of Science, 2015 Sports Leadership and Management

SKILLS

- · Customer service
- · Customer communication
- · Outside & Inside Sales
- · Sales management
- Recruiting and Hiring
- Inventory management
- · Profit & Loss management
- Budget management
- Staff training and development